Now, that we know how many temporaries or intermediate values we need
现在，我们知道需要多少临时值或中间值
to evaluate a function and we also know where those intermediate value is going to
对函数求值，我们还知道这些中间值将在哪里
be stored in activation record. The last thing we need to know in order to code generation
存储在激活记录中。为了生成代码，我们需要知道的最后一件事是
is how many temporaries are in use at each point in the program. Change colors
是程序中每个点使用的临时文件的数量。更改颜色
here and so the way we're going to do that is we're going to add a new argument
我们要做的就是在这里添加一个新的参数
to co-generation which is the position of the next available temporary.
去热电联产，这是下一个可供临时使用的位置。
So as temporaries gets used up, this argument, the co-generation will change while
因此，随着时间的耗尽，这种争论，联产将会改变，而
other expressions to save their values and save places without stepping on
其他表达式，用于保存它们的值和保存位置，而不需要执行任何操作
temporaries that are already having saved by all other expressions. And as you'll see
已由所有其他表达式保存的临时文件。正如你会看到的
in a, in a moment here when we do an example, the temporary area of the activation
在a中，在我们举个例子的时候，激活的临时区域
r ecord is going to be used like a small fixed size stack. Essentially,
Record将像一个小的固定大小的堆栈一样使用。从本质上讲，
we're going to have the same stack discipline that we had before only all
我们将拥有与之前相同的堆栈规则
the computation on the stack pointer, all the discussion, all the computation of
堆栈指针的计算，所有的讨论，所有的计算
what all sets to use has already been done by the compiler. So, what we used to do by
编译器已经完成了所有集合要使用的内容。所以，我们过去做的是
pushing and popping element from the stack in the generated code allow that computation
在生成的代码中从堆栈推送和弹出元素允许该计算
has been moved into the compiler and all that happens now is a bunch
已经移到编译器中了，现在发生的一切都是一堆
of stores and load. To fix off that from the frame pointer So let's take a look
储存和装货。把它从帧指针中去掉，让我们来看看
at how this works. Here's the code that we had for e1 + e2 under the old scheme
这是怎么运作的。这是我们在旧方案下针对e1+e2的代码
where we didn't have a separate area in the activation records for temporaries.
我们在临时激活记录中没有单独的区域。
So we would generate a code for e1, and then we would save the results
因此，我们将为E1生成代码，然后保存结果
of e1 on the stack, and that would be done by saving the value of the accumulator under
的值，这可以通过将累加器的值保存在
the stack and then we would have to adjust the stack pointer And then after we
堆栈，然后我们必须调整堆栈指针，然后在我们
had evaluated the two, then we would load the results of e1 back into a temporary register,
评估了这两个参数后，我们会将E1的结果加载回临时寄存器，
we could do the add And then we could pop the value off of the stack, the
我们可以做加法，然后我们可以从堆栈中弹出值，
intermediate value off of the stack Down to the new scheme. Co-generations going to
从堆栈向下移至新方案的中间值。共同世代将走向
take a second argument saying what is the position of the next available temporary so
使用第二个参数，说明下一个可用临时So的位置是什么
what is the position of the next unused temporary inside of the activation record
激活记录中下一个未使用的临时文件的位置是什么
and so now we generate code for e1 and we pass along the argument okay because e1 may
现在我们为E1生成代码，我们传递参数，因为E1可能
itself have some temporaries that it needs to store And, and then after you [inaudible]
它本身有一些需要存储的时间，然后在你之后[听不见]
to evaluating, now we just do a direct store into, into the activation record
要进行评估，现在我们只需直接存储到激活记录中
at all set empty from the frame pointer And so now as we have to do in store,
从帧指针开始完全设置为空，因此现在正如我们必须在存储器中所做的那样，
we have to save e1 in the activation record so we have it for later
我们必须将E1保存在激活记录中，以便稍后使用
on but we have to do any manipulation of the stacks. So, we could place two instructions
但我们必须对堆栈进行任何操作。因此，我们可以放置两条指令
here by one And then we generate code for e2 but now. We just save
这里是1，然后我们为e2生成代码，但是现在。我们只是省了点钱
the temporary value at position at, at all set empty from the frame pointer so the next
位于的位置的临时值从帧指针开始设置为空，因此下一个
available temporary would be of address empty o r offset, excuse me, nt+4
可用的临时地址为空或偏移量，对不起，NT+4
And then after each was evaluating, now we have to load the value of e1 back into a temporary
然后在每次求值之后，现在我们必须将e1的值加载回临时
and again that was all set NT from the frame pointer of the current activation
同样，这都是从当前激活的帧指针设置的NT
record and then we can do the add and once again we saved the manipulation
记录，然后我们可以执行添加操作，并再次保存操作
of the stack pointers. So this code sequence here is two instructions
堆栈指针的。所以这里的代码序列是两条指令
shorter than the one we had before and this actually substantially more
比我们之前的要短，而这个实际上要多得多
efficient.
效率很高。